Oh
Oh
Oh baby
Oh baby
When I'm completely lost in your eyes
너의 두 눈 속에 내가 가득할 땐
I feel like I've got the whole world, yeah
세상을 다 가진 듯한 기분 yeah
In this overwhelming excitement, I dream again
벅찬 설렘 속에 또다시 꿈꾸곤 해 ooh
An endless dream called you
끝이 없는 너란 꿈
The precious feeling called love
사랑이라는 소중한 마음
Without you, I wouldn't know
너 아니면 몰라
It's just a fleeting emotion
그저 흘러가 버릴 감정일 뿐야
You awaken me
넌 날 깨워내
You always make my heart race anew, you're mine
늘 새롭게 가슴 뛰게 해 you're mine
You're the only answer for me
너 만이 내 답인 거야
Even if eternity doesn't exist, yeah
영원은 없다 해도 yeah
I won't believe it
믿지 않을 거라고
Baby, just like the first feeling, always love me more
Baby 처음 느낌 그대로 늘 love me more
Even as time passes, I'm still yours
시간이 흘러도 난 여전히 너야
Oh baby, like an unending dream, love me more
Oh baby 멎지 않을 꿈결처럼 love me more
As if it's a dream that will last forever
영원히 계속될 꿈인 듯이
Just like this, love me more
이대로만 love me more
Forever, love me more
영원토록 love me more
Oh, love me more
Ooh love me more
Just like now, love forever
지금처럼 love forever
Love me more
Love me more
Just like this, love me more
이대로만 love me more
As if it's a dream that will last forever
영원히 계속될 꿈인 듯이
The world I faced, blossomed because of you
너로 인해 핀 채 마주했던 이 세상
Do you know how much your love has illuminated me?
이토록 날 빛낸 너의 그 사랑 넌 알까
This moment is complete because you're here
네가 있어 완성되는 이 순간
I want to whisper to you too
너에게도 속삭여 주고 싶어
Even if eternity doesn't exist, yeah
영원은 없다 해도 yeah
I won't believe it, baby yeah
믿지 않을 거라고 baby yeah
Just like the first feeling, always love me more
처음 느낌 그대로 늘 love me more
Even as time passes, I'm still yours
시간이 흘러도 난 여전히 너야
Oh baby, like an unending dream, love me more
Oh baby 멎지 않을 꿈결처럼 love me more
As if it's a dream that will last forever
영원히 계속될 꿈인 듯이
Just like this, love me more
이대로만 love me more
Forever, love me more
영원토록 love me more
Oh, love me more
Ooh love me more
Just like now, love forever
지금처럼 love forever
Love me more
Love me more
Just like this, love me more
이대로만 love me more
As if it's a dream that will last forever
영원히 계속될 꿈인 듯이